Guide to the Paper Tiger Television Records MSS.276
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. Activities, 1978-2012; 49.6 Linear Feet in 38 record cartons, 15 oversize folders, 7 cassette boxes, 5 flat boxes, and 4 manuscript boxes.; 26 U-matic; 20 Hi8; 17 MiniDV; 5 VHS; 1 Betacam; 1 Betacam_SP; 2.87 Megabytes in 123 files.
  - Subseries II.C: Workshops and Conferences, 1985-2012
    - NAMAC and media summer program, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - NAMAC - newsletter, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - NAMAC - youth, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - New Neutral Zone Report - workshop, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Next 5 Minutes - conference, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - New Strategies DMC, Detroit, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - New York City Grassroots Media conference, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - NFCLP Spring conference, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Oligopoly cards, Undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Open Forum, New York City, 2012 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Open Society Institute U.S. programs, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Paper Tiger TV workshop curriculum, Undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Paper Tiger Productions workshop - evaluations, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Plato Royalty Lecture at Evergreen State College, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - The Point workshop, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Police Accountablilty Project, Undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Press Packet - Occupation and Intervention: perspectives on the Middle East, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Production handouts for workshops, Undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Project Reach, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - "Public Access / Public Radio: Using Airwaves…" Conference, New York, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Queeruption - flyers, Undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Queeruption - Homo economics, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Queeruption - Queeruption Gay Expo, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Queeruption - Tara meeting notes / volunteer sheet, Undated (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Queeruption - Timeline, Undated (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Roots - Military Myths workshop materials, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Roots - video open house evaluation, Undated (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Roots - video / media lit resources, Undated (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Self-description cards, Undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - "Senses of Home: Dialogue within communities" program - photo, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Social Theory, Politics, and the Arts conference, Undated (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Socialist Scholars Conference, 1997-1999
      - "Contemporary Feminism and Its Discontents" Panel, Part one, March 29, 1997 (Box 186, Hi8 276_1493)
      - "Contemporary Feminism and Its Discontents" Panel, Part two, March 29, 1997 (Box 186, Hi8 276_1494)
      - "The Crisis in Kosovo" Panel, April 10, 1999 (Box 188, Hi8 276_1568)
      - "The Crisis in Kosovo" Q+A, Part two, April, 1999 (Box 80, U-matic ID: 276.0392)
      - "The Crisis in Kosovo" Q+A, Part two -- Aleander Burgalin, Omar Dahbour, Mathew Ally, Kam Eshy, April, 1999 (Box 80, U-matic ID: 276.0393)
      - "The Truth About Kosovo and NATO Expansion" Panel, April 10, 1999 (Box 184, Hi8 276_1383)
    - "Speaking Truth to Power: Media Justice in Our Communities" Conference, NYC, March 2, 2008 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Standing with Palestine project binder, Undated (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Standing with Palestine - workshop material, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Streetwork workshop, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - "Steppin' in 2 Manhood" Conference, Sussex County, New Jersey, undated
      - Paper materials (Box 100, Folder 16)
      - Workshop PSA (Box 185, Minidv 276_1419)
    - Subcomandante Marcos message, Undated (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - TeacHarlem II at City College of New York, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - "A Time to Act" youth conference, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Training for Transformation workshop, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Truce, Undated (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Truce (Military Myths), Undated (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Tumblebug TV Workshops, December 8-9, 1990
      - Press conference, News Interviews, December 8, 1990 (Box 109, U-matic 276_0613)
      - Silent vigil in Balboa Park, San Diego, December 9, 1990 (Box 109, U-matic 276_0608)
    - Union for Democratic Communications annual meeting poster, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Union for Democratic Communication conference, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Video Production curriculum, Undated (Box 12, Folder 56A)
    - Workshop curriculum file - learning exercises, Undated (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Workshop curriculum file - loose papers, Undated (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Workshop trip -- Denise and Tara, Sin Sin Naughty, undated (Box 82, Hi8 276_0447)
    - World Communications conference, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Youth Force, Undated (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Youth Peace Workshop, Undated (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Youth Summit, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Subseries II.D: Film Festivals and Screenings, 1982-2012
    Subseries II.D Film Festivals and Screenings (1982-2012) contains records relating to the film festivals and screenings that Paper Tiger organized and participated in. These files include ephemera, such as schedules, flyers, and posters; applications for festivals; and video edits and compilations used for such events.
    Subseries II.D Film Festivals and Screenings (1982-2012) is arranged alphabetically.
    - Access Orbit Screenings, 2000-2001
      - E.D.G.E. Screening, undated (Box 187, Minidv 276_1551)
      - Photo boards, 2000 (Folder 7 Left)
      - Paper materials, Undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Screening, December 2, 2000 (Box 187, Minidv 276_0912)
      - Screening, December 16, 2000 (Box 187, Minidv 276_0913)
      - Screening, January 13, 2001 (Box 187, Minidv 276_0915)
      - Screening, January 13, 2001 (Box 187, Minidv 276_0914)
      - Screening, 2001 (Box 187, Minidv 276_0916)
    - Alliance for Community Media screenings, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - American Film Institute video festival, 1988-1994 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - American Museum of Natural History - "Senses of Home" screening, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - "Amerika" screenings, Undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Ann Arbor Film Festivals, Undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Art, Activism and Analysis Tour, California, February 2008 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Athens Film Festival, 1995-1999 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Atlanta Film and Video Festival, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Atlanta Film Festival, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Austin Gay and Lesbian International Film Festival, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Awards, Undated (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - BACA's 22nd Annual Film and Video Festival poster, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Big Girls -- Screening Flyer, 2000 (Box 102, Folder 24)
    - Big Muddy Film Festival - poster, 1994, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Black Maria Film and Video Festival, Undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Black Women and Invisibility films poster, Undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Brainwash Movie Festival, Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Brecht Forum - Military Myths, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Bronx Museum of the Arts, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Brooklyn Art Council (BACA) Annual Film and Video Festival, Undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Brooklyn College screening, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Brooklyn Underground Film Festival, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Canada screening - Smashing the Myths...and Staking a Claim in Cyberspace, Undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Casualties of War - screening info, Undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Central Florida Film and Video Festival poster, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Chicago International Telvision Competition, 1998-1999, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Cinemambiente Festival, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Conference Screenings, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - "Confronting Dis-ease through the Mediated Body" film festival - Felt Evidence, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence regarding screenings, Undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - CUNY RTTC Screening, January 11, 2010
      - Tape one (Box 186, Minidv 276_1517)
      - Tape two (Box 186, Minidv 276_1516)
    - CYPHER - Fenced Out screening, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Dallas Video Festival poster, 2000 (Folder 33)
    - Dallas Video Festival - Showdown in Seattle, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Do it Your Damn Self - National Youth Film and Video Festival, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - "Fat is Beautiful" Screenings, Bluestockings, 1999-2000
      - Paper materials, Undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - Post-screening discussion, March 21, 2000 (Box 184, Minidv 276_1305)
      - U-matic recording, June 18, 1999 (Box 177, U-matic 276_1914)
      - VHS recording, circa 2000 (Box 115, Vhs 276_0716)
    - Feminist Film Festivals, Undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Fenced Out / Homecoming Queens / Keep on Livin' -- Screening, 1999-2002 (Box 140, Betacam sp 276_1375)
    - Festivals / Awards, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Festivals not in, Undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Fifth Montbeliard International Video and Television Festival, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Films of Resistance - "Putting the 'Demo' back in Democracy" screening, Undated (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Flaming Film Festival, 2002-2005 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Fledgling Film Festival, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Foreign screenings, Undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Fringe Film Festival, 1993-1995 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Garden Screening, August 26, 2010
      - Tape one (Box 187, Minidv 276_0964)
      - Tape two (Box 181, Minidv 276_0965)
    - Gay and Lesbian Film Festivals, 1996, 2000-2003 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Gay and Lesbian Film Festivals, 2004-2006 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Gurl Film Festival, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Hampshire College screenings, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Hamptons International Film Festival - Homecoming Queens, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Hip Hop Odyssey International Film Festival, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Homecoming Queens - screenings, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Hometown Video Festival, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Hometown Video Festival, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Hometown Video Festival - finalist certificate, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Hometown USA Video Festival poster, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Houston International Film Festival poster, 1990 (Folder 30)
    - Howard U. Audio, Film, and Video Festival and Competition, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Human Rights Watch International Film Festival, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Human Rights Watch International Film Festival - Press Report, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Image News Film / Video Center, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Images Film Festival - Military Myths, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Inside Out Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival, Toronto, May 17-27, 2007 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - Inside Out Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival -- Backalley Jukebox, Undated (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - International Documentary Film Festival - El Tude Verdade, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Ithaca Summer School of the Arts screening - Tara Mateik, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Jeoju International Film Festival - Korea, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - "Labor Intensive" film series, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Lady Fest - invoice, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Loco Motion International Film Festival, 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Lower East Side Girls Club, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Margaret Mead Film and Video Festival, 1997, undated
      - Paper materials, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 52)
      - Video edit -- "Showdown in Seattle," "Breaking the Bank," Crandi's footage of Media Mogul Tour, undated (Box 81, U-matic 276_0411)
    - Market This! screening, Undated (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Medgar Evers College - screening, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Media Matters, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Military Myths World Premier, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Military Myths screenings, Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous screenings and film festivals, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Miscellaneous screenings and film festivals, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Miscellaneous screenings and film festivals, 1993-1995 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Miscellaneous screenings and film festivals, 1996-1999 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Miscellaneous screenings and film festivals, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Miscellaneous screenings and film festivals, 2001-2004 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Miscellaneous screenings and film festivals, 2005-2006 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Miscellaneous screenings and film festivals, Undated (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Mother Courage Tour, 1990, undated
      - Excerpts, undated (Box 111, U-matic 276_0637)
      - Last night of tour, interview with Jordanian women, undated (Box 117, U-matic 276_0806)
      - Last day, undated (Box 180, Hi8 276_1043)
      - Tisch Auditorium, February 7, 1990 (Box 117, U-matic 276_0805)
    - Museum of Television and Radio - Fenced Out, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - National Educational Media Network, 1995-1998 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - National Art, Activism, and Analysis tour - Paper Tiger reads Paper Tiger, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - New York City - local screenings, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - New York Free Media Alliance screenings, Undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - New York Lesbian and Gay Film Festival, 1999-2003 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - North Star Fund screenings - Shared Histories, Undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Occupy the Film Festival, 2012 (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - Open Center Screening, IMC Video, 1999-2001
      - Screening tape (Box 82, Vhs 276_0424)
      - Screening tape (Box 82, Vhs 276_0425)
      - Screening tape -- Master, March 15, 2001 (Box 167, U-matic 276_0418)
        1. Showdown in Seattle (Big Noise); 2. Breaking the Bank (PTTV/HAVC); 3. Melbourne Rising (SKA TV); 4. Not My President (IMC NYC); 5. Chiapas 12/31/2000 (Big Noise)
    - Operation Class War screening - poster, Undated (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - The Other America Film Festival, Undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Outfest, 2007 (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - Palestine screening - Rock Paper Missiles, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Pandæmonium: Biennial of Moving Images, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Paper Tiger TV course outline, Undated (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Peace and Human Security Media Festival, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Project Reach Youth, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Queer Youth Nation - TV or not TV..., 2002 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - "Race, Crime, and the Media" screening, Undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Recording / Transmission, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Rock Paper Missiles screening, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Rotterdam Film Festival, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Rotterdam Film Festival poster, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - San Diego - Baja California Latino Film Festival, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - San Francisco Art Institute - In Progress, 1992-1993 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - San Francisco International Lesbian and Gay Film Festival, Undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Sarah Lawrence Film and Video Festival, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Sarah Lawrence College Experimental Film and Video Festival - poster, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Screenings -- Correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - Screenings -- Facilitation Tips, 2000 (Box 100, Folder 22)
    - Screenings -- Flyers, 2003-2012 (Box 100, Folder 23)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1982-1983 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Screenings - Mixed, 1983-1984 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Screenings - Mixed, 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Screenings - Mixed, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Screenings - Mixed, 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1990 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Screenings - Mixed, 1991-1992 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Screenings - Mixed, 1993-1996 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1995-1996 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Screenings -- Press Coverage, 2008-2009 (Box 100, Folder 24)
    - Seoul Human Rights Film Festival, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Seoul Human Rights Film Festival, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Seoul International Film Festival, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Shedhalle, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Sleeth Gallery, 1996 (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Social Justice Film Festival, Seattle, April 24-26, 2009 (Box 100, Folder 25)
    - Stop the War Festival, Theatre for New City, February 9, 1991
      - #538B (Box 125, U-matic 276_1071)
      - #538A, Part one (Box 125, U-matic 276_1073)
      - #538A, Part two (Box 125, U-matic 276_1072)
    - Subcomandante Marcos, Undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Subverting Media screenings, Undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Summer Screening Series, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Summer Screening Series, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Taos Talking Pictures Festival, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Taos Talking Pictures Festival, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Teen Screen Image Atlanta, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - "Third Annual CSUSM Student Video Festival" - poster, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Three Rivers Arts Festival, 1990-1995 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Tribeca Film Festival, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Turning Tragedy into War - MOMA screening, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Urban Visionaries Festival, 2000 (Box 116, U-matic 276_0784)
    - Urban Visionaries Festival, 2002
      - Paper materials (Box 14, Folder 38)
      - Video compilation -- Military Myths, Fenced Out, Biorhythms (Box 162, U-matic 276_1757)
    - Urban Visionaries Festival -- My World, Journeys, 2003 (Box 79, U-matic 276_0380)
    - USA Film Festival, 1995-1999 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - VC Film Fest, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Whitney - New American Film and Video Series, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Whitney - PTTV screenings, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - "Propaganda / Whitney" screening, Undated (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - "The Unionist" - Labor Film Festival announcement, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - United States Film Festival, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Video Shorts Festival - poster and program, c. 1988 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Who's Paying the Price screenings, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - "Women Direct" - Films by Women, c. 1983 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Women in the Director's Chair - Film and Video Festival, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Woodstock screenings, Undated (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - Youth film festivals, Undated (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Youth Media Arts NYC - Urban Visionaries, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Youth Media Jam, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- Series III. Publicity, 1982-2013; 43.3 Linear Feet in 36 record cartons, 7 oversize folders, 3 manuscript boxes, 2 flat boxes, and 2 cassette boxes.; 652 Megabytes in 696 files.; 67 U-matic; 13 VHS; 2 MiniDV; 2 Betacam; 1 Betamax
  Series III. Publicity (1982-2013) contains both press and promotional materials for Paper Tiger TV, including published articles, advertisements, graphic design, promotional ephemera, outreach materials, and promotional videos.
  - Subseries III.A: Press, 1982-2002
    Subseries III.A Press (1982-2002) contains published articles, reviews, and advertisements about Paper Tiger TV and its programming.
    Subseries III.A Press (1982-2002) is arranged alphabetically by the title of the publication.
    - ABC CLIO video reviews, Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - The Advocate and Greenwich Time (Connecticut), 1991 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Afterimage / AFI, 1983-1987 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Afterimage - "Mogul World Tour" - DeeDee Halleck, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Afterimage - "PTTV Meets the Press", 1983 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Afterimage - "Youth and the Media", 1990-1993 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Alter Net - article proposal, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Alternative Media, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Alternative TV and The Gulf War -- Simone Farkhondeh, Somerville Community Access TV, April 27, 1991 (Box 116, Vhs 276_0795)
    - American Film, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Art Com articles, Undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - ArtForum, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - ArtPaper, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Art Papers - Virginia (Key Gallery), 1991 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Article dub masters, Undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Atlanta Journal, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Audio Visuelle Media - Rotterdam, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Austin Access - annotated, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Australian TV Interview with Simone, Gulf Crisis TV Project, undated (Box 116, Vhs 276_0794)
    - BRC News, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Brecht Forum 25th Anniversary Journal - Access Orbit advertisement, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - "California Student Ln." - publications with PTTV reviews, 1983-1988 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Camera Austria, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Check Point, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Cockburn article - Alternative Press Published, c. 1987 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Cologne, Germany, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Columbia Journalism Review, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - The Columbus Dispatch, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Com Pact, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Bill Boddy's article in "Communications" - Paris, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Community Media Review, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Complete Gulf Crisis TV Project set of articles (DeeDee Halleck), Undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Crash, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Cultures in Contention, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Dallas Observer, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Days of Decision, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - DeeDee Halleck interview in "In These Times", 1991 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Deep Dish TV - with PTTV mention, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Deep Dish TV - with PTTV mention, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Dénonciation - French journal, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Discourse - on Born to be Sold, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Downtown Resident, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Downtown, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - FFWD, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Film Festival News - "Paper Tiger Roams City", 1987 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - FYI - DeeDee Halleck on the Public Sphere, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Freeing the Media, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - From VTR to Cyberspace, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Fuse, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - The Georgia Straight, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Gramma (Cuban film/video festival), 1985 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - The Guardian, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - The Guardian, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Gulf Crisis TV article - "People's Weekly World", 1991 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Gulf Crisis TV mentions, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Gulf Crisis TV newspaper clippings, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Gulf Press Copies, Undated (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Hartford Courant, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - High Performance, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Image News - Atlanta, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - ImMediaTe Impact, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - ImMediaTe Impact, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - In Pittsburgh, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - In These Times [and other articles], Undated (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - In These Times - on DeeDee Halleck, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - The Independent, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 59)